Inventory of the Richard De Rochemont papers, 1900-1997
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series IV. Films, 1936-1972
  - Sub-series 3. French Government Tourist Office, 1955-1964
    - "Chateau Country" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - "Chateau Country" (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Chateau Country" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (color), 1958 (Box 25)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (color), 1958 (Box 57)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (color original rolls), undated (Box 58)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - "Contrasts of Carcassonne" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - "Corsica" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - "Cruise Through Paris" (color), 1955 (Box 57)
    - Cuts, trims, and outs (color), circa 1956-1961 (Box 48-50)
    - "D.B. In Paris" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - "Destination Alsace" (b&w), 1959 (Box 2)
    - "Destination Alsace" (color), undated (Box 30)
    - "Destination Alsace" (color), undated (Box 32)
    - "Destination Alsace" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 63)
    - "Destination Alsace" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - "Destination Alsace" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 80)
    - "Destination Alsace" (sound), undated (Box 77)
    - "Destination Alsace" outs and trims, undated (Box 99)
    - "Diversity of France" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "Diversity of France" (color original), undated (Box 53)
    - "Fine Food - Good Wine" (b&w), 1955 (Box 4)
    - "Fine Food - Good Wine" (color), 1955 (Box 25)
    - "Food and Motoring, part II" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - "France for the Sportsman" (color), undated (Box 24)
    - "France for the Sportsman" (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "France for the Sportsman" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 10)
    - "France for the Sportsman" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 63)
    - "France for the Sportsman" (sound), undated (Box 78)
    - "French Caribbean" (color), undated (Box 23)
    - "French Caribbean" (color), 1964 (Box 29)
    - "French Caribbean" (color original rolls), undated (Box 58)
    - "French Caribbean" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 63)
    - "French Caribbean" (sound), undated (Box 77)
    - "French Foods" (color), undated (Box 26)
    - "French Tourism, Food and Motoring" (color), undated (Box 23)
    - "Glimpses of Normandy" (color), 1956 (Box 22)
    - "Glimpses of Normandy" (color), 1956 (Box 57)
    - "It's Convention Time In France" (color), 1958 (Box 30)
    - "It's Convention Time In France" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - "Lafayette" (color), 1956 (Box 57)
    - "Lafayette" - outs, trims, and cuts (color), undated (Box 56)
    - "Lafayette" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - "Magic of Les Baux" (color), 1957 (Box 22)
    - "Magic of Les Baux" (color), 1957 (Box 26)
    - "Magic of Les Baux" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - "Magic of Les Baux" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - "Magic of Les Baux" (sound), undated (Box 76)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), circa 1956-1957 (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), 1957 (Box 46-47)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), 1957 (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), 1959 (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), 1961 (Box 44-46)
    - Miscellaneous original rolls (color), 1961 (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous shots (color inter-negative), 1955 (Box 64)
    - "Motoring Mood" (color), 1955 (Box 23)
    - "Motoring Mood" (color), 1955 (Box 57)
    - "New Corsica" (color), 1959 (Box 32)
    - "New Corsica" (color), undated (Box 57)
    - "New Corsica" (color original rolls), undated (Box 38)
    - "New Corsica" - outs, trims, and cuts (color), undated (Box 55)
    - "New Corsica" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 13)
    - "New Corsica" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - "Normandy" (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Normandy" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - "Normandy" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - "Oldest Paris" (color), 1957 (Box 25-26)
    - "Oldest Paris" (color), 1957 (Box 32)
    - "Oldest Paris" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - "Oldest Paris" (sound), 1957 (Box 2)
    - "Painters of Paris" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - "Paris - Boy's Eye View" (color), 1959 (Box 30-32)
    - "Paris - Boy's Eye View" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - "Paris - Boy's Eye View" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 62)
    - "Paris - Boy's Eye View" (sound), undated (Box 2)
    - "Paris - Boy's Eye View" (sound), undated (Box 76)
    - "Paris 14 July" (sound), undated (Box 76)
    - "Paris of the Painters" (color), undated (Box 27)
    - "Paris of the Painters" (color), 1956 (Box 30)
    - "Paris of the Painters" (color original), undated (Box 53)
    - "Paris of the Painters" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 13)
    - "Paris Today" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - "Paris Today" (color), undated (Box 57)
    - "Paris Today" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 62)
    - "Paris" (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Paris" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" (color), 1960 (Box 28)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" (color), undated (Box 57)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" - outs, trims, and cuts (color), undated (Box 55)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - "Peaceful Valley of the Loire" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - "Rivers of France" (sound), undated (Box 78)
    - "Riviera" (color original rolls), undated (Box 43)
    - "Riviera" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - "Riviera of France" (b&w), undated (Box 9)
    - "Riviera Playground" (color), 1955 (Box 25)
    - "Riviera Playground" (color), 1955 (Box 57)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" (color), 1958 (Box 29)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - "Roussillon Folkways" - reels 1 and 2 (color), undated (Box 100)
    - Seine, Riviera, Spring In Paris (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "Seine River" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - "Shopping In Paris" (color), 1956 (Box 27-28)
    - "Shopping In Paris" (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "Shopping In Paris" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - "Smiles of Paris" (color), 1961 (Box 101)
    - "Spotlight on French Spas" (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Spotlight on French Spas" (color), 1961 (Box 27)
    - "Spotlight on French Spas" (color), 1961 (Box 30)
    - "Spotlight on French Spas" (color original rolls), undated (Box 58)
    - "Spotlight on French Spas" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - "Springtime in Paris" (b&w), undated (Box 4-5)
    - "Springtime in Paris" (b&w), undated (Box 7)
    - "Springtime In Paris" (sound), undated (Box 78)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (b&w), 1958 (Box 9)
    - "Summertime in the French Alps" (color), 1958 (Box 30)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 10)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - "Summertime In the French Alps" (sound), undated (Box 76-77)
    - "Thermalism" (b&w), undated (Box 102-103)
    - Untitled (b&w), undated (Box 16)
    - "Vacation In France" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "Vacation In France" (sound), undated (Box 76)
    - "Visit to Basque Country" (color), 1956 (Box 21)
    - "Visit to Basque Country" (color original rolls), undated (Box 42)
    - "Visit to Basque Country" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 13)
    - "Welcome to France" (color), 1964 (Box 30)
    - "Welcome to France" (color original rolls), undated (Box 58)
    - "Welcome to France" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - "Welcome to France" (sound), undated (Box 78)
    - "Women of France" (b&w), 1958 (Box 7)
    - "Women of France" (color), 1958 (Box 30)
    - "Women of France" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - "Women of France" (color original rolls), undated (Box 43)
    - "Women of France" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 62)
    - "Women of France" (sound), undated (Box 79)
  - Sub-series 4. Informational and other, 1952-1972, undated
    Arranged alphabetically. Contains films, primarily informational, produced for various companies and organizations by De Rochemont, Vavin, Inc., and Louis De Rochemont’s production company. Organizations for which De Rochemont produced informational films include American Iron and Steel Institute, Mobil Oil Corporation, and the Moroccan Ministry of Tourism.
    - "14th of July" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "14th of July" (b&w), undated (Box 7)
    - "14th of July" (sound), undated (Box 77)
    - "1776 - France-America" (color), undated (Box 57)
    - "Agnew" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - Air France - "Air To Air" (color original rolls), undated (Box 43)
    - Air France - "Air to Air" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 11)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (color), undated (Box 27)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (color), undated (Box 32)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (color original rolls), undated (Box 43)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 10)
    - Air France - "Five Steps to the Jets" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 61)
    - Air France - stock shots (color original rolls), undated (Box 39)
    - Air France - stock shots (color inter-negative), undated (Box 63)
    - "Alps" - Larry Sherman (color), undated (Box 84-85)
    - "Ambassadors For Friendship" (color), undated (Box 31)
    - "America's Williamsburg" (color), undated (Box 32)
    - "America's Williamsburg" (color), undated (Box 86)
    - American Cancer Society - "Second Voice" (color), undated (Box 24)
    - American Petroleum Institute - "Broken Bow Story" (color), undated (Box 24)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Airplane Hangar"/"New Home for 747" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Blood Bank"/"Five Lives Might Be Saved" (color), undated (Box 30)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Blood Bank"/"Five Lives Might Be Saved" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Bridge"/"Bridge of the Future" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Butler School"/"School with a Difference" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Central Containerization" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Chapel"/"Unique Chapel Completed" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Containerization"/"Revolution in Freight Handling" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Design Awards"/"Design in Steel Awards Announced" (color), undated (Box 31)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Design Award"/"Design in Steel Awards Announced" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Foreign Steel" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Garden House"/"Storage Problem Solved" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Guard Rail"/"Safer Roads for the Future" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Guard Rail"/"Safer Roads for the Future" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Steel Imports" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Steel Imports" (color), undated (Box 27)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Steel Imports" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Minnesota Farm"/"New Life for the Small Farm" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Minnesota Farm"/"New Life for the Small Farm" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Mushrooms"/"Mushroom Industry" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Mushrooms"/"Mushroom Industry" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Novelty Cans" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Rye School"/"New Approach to School Construction" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Rye School"/"New Approach to School Construction" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 70)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Shrimps"/"Shrimp Canning Centennial" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Steel - '67 Expo" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute - "Wire Sculpture"/"Artistry in Wire" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 59)
    - American Society of Travel Agents (ASTA) - "Innocents Abroad: A Modern Tale of Travel" (color), 1958 (Box 24)
    - American Society of Travel Agents (ASTA) - "Innocents Abroad: A Modern Tale of Travel" (color), undated (Box 32)
    - American Society of Travel Agents (ASTA) - "Innocents Abroad" (color original rolls), undated (Box 58)
    - American Society of Travel Agents (ASTA) - "Innocents Abroad" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 12)
    - American Society of Travel Agents (ASTA) - "Innocents Abroad" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 62)
    - American Trial Lawyers Association - "Wright Speech" (sound), undated (Box 80)
    - Army film of newsreel trip - "European Report" (b&w), undated (Box 7)
    - "Bachelor Party" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - "Bachelor Party" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - "Basque Country" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "Basque Country" (color), undated (Box 32)
    - "Basque Country" (sound), undated (Box 76)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 67)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 87-88)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Country Wines of France" (sound), undated (Box 75)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Print Festival" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Print Festival" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 67)
    - Bell & Stanton, Inc. - "Print Festival" (sound), undated (Box 78)
    - "Body Painting" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - "Body Painting" (color original rolls), undated (Box 38)
    - "Boscobel" (color), undated (Box 23)
    - "Brancusi Exhibition at Guggenheim Museum" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - "Chance to Live" (b&w), undated (Box 4)
    - "City Room" (color), 1959 (Box 33)
    - "Classifieds: America's Marketplace" (color), 1959 (Box 33)
    - Consumers Union - "Consumers Want To Know" (color), undated (Box 31)
    - Consumers Union - "Consumers Want To Know" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - "Convention" (color), undated (Box 33)
    - "Convention" (sound), undated (Box 73)
    - CPC Aida (color original rolls), undated (Box 39)
    - CPC Aida - Vienna Show (color), undated (Box 89)
    - "Creating Tomorrow's Cities" (color originals), undated (Box 90)
    - "De Gaulle Crossing the Rhine" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "Diller" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 66)
    - Encyclopedia (b&w), undated (Box 9)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica - "Development of Transportation" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - Enjay Chemical Company - "Clean Seas Ahead" (color), undated (Box 28)
    - Enjay Chemical Company - "Clean Seas Ahead" (color), undated (Box 24)
    - Enjay Chemical Company - "Escoweld" (color), undated (Box 23)
    - Esso Chemical - "Flit" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 64)
    - Esso Chemical - "Ex-Grouting" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 69)
    - Esso Chemical - "Science Awards", undated (Box 91-92)
    - Esso Chemical - "Science Awards" (sound), undated (Box 75)
    - "Ethyl Lead" (color), undated (Box 93)
    - "Ethyl Lead" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 67)
    - "Ethyl Lead" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 94)
    - "Ex-Manhattan" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - Farley Manning Association - "Teenage Sundae Party" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 60)
    - "Flemington" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - "Fleuves de France" (b&w), undated (Box 6)
    - "Flying Family" (color), undated (Box 28)
    - French Lines -" Normandy Towns" and French Railways - "Au Pays du Bien Manger" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - French Wine Industry - "Party at the Potters" (b&w), undated (Box 6)
    - French Wine Industry - "Party at the Potters" (color), 1957 (Box 26)
    - "Gatorade" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 69)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Coffee Hour, Puerto Rican Style" (color), undated (Box 21)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Coffee On the Rocks" (color), undated (Box 21)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Delicious Snack - In a Jiffy" (color), undated (Box 20)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Desserts and Salads - Quicker Than Ever" (color), undated (Box 20)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Have a Dinner Party the Easy Way" (color), undated (Box 20)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Mealtime Budget Stretcher" (color), undated (Box 21)
    - General Foods Kitchen - "Rice Takes to the Road" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - General Motors - "Motorama", 1956 (Box 104)
    - General Motors - "Motorama 1956" (b&w) (Box 4)
    - General Motors - "Motorama" (b&w), undated (Box 5)
    - "Grasslands Farming" (b&w), undated (Box 9)
    - Guffanti Film Laboratories - "Motoring" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - GW Cabinet - Parade (b&w), 1972 (Box 4)
    - "Houston Museum" (b&w), 1963 (Box 6)
    - "Houston Museum" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - Houston Museum of Fine Arts - "Road to the Olmec Head" (color), undated (Box 105)
    - Houston Museum of Fine Arts - "Road To the Olmec-Head" (color), undated (Box 26)
    - Houston Museum of Fine Arts - "Road To the Olmec-Head" (color original rolls), undated (Box 39)
    - Houston Museum of Fine Arts - "Road to the Olmec-Head" (sound), undated (Box 80)
    - "If You Are First At the Crash" (sound), 1960 August (Box 1)
    - J.C. Penney - "Fashion Capsule: 72" (color), undated (Box 2)
    - J.C. Penney - "Fashion Capsule: 72" (color), 1972 (Box 26)
    - J.C. Penney - "Home Of Dreams" (color), undated (Box 22)
    - Julius Wile - "Season of Magic" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - Julius Wile - "Season of Magic" (sound), undated (Box 79)
    - "King Mohammed V of Morocco" (b&w), undated (Box 4)
    - "King Mohammed V of Morocco" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 10)
    - "Kip Catches Up" (color), 1965 (Box 24)
    - "Kip Catches Up" (color), undated (Box 31)
    - "Le Bourgeois Gentilhomme" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 81)
    - "Life Harris" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 68)
    - "Life Space" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - "Light Upon the Earth" (b&w), undated (Box 4)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Appliance Repair" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Applying for a Job" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "As Maine Goes" (color), undated (Box 35)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Auto Trades" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Business Machines" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Careers In Health" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Cooks and Chefs" (color), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Hotels and Motels," "Jobs in Baking," "Sheet Metal" (inter-negative), undated (Box 107)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Job Corps and You" (color), 1971 (Box 35)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Job Developer" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Jobs In Cosmetology" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Jobs In Drafting" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Jobs in Welding" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Lost Boundaries", undated (Box 108-109)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Lost Boundaries" (color), undated (Box 36)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "M.O.T.A." (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Machine Trades" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Manpower Training Act" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Neighborhood Youth Corps" (color), undated (Box 35)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Opportunities In Clerical Work" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Parlons François Lecon" (color), undated (Box 35)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - Louis de Rochemont films - "Sales and Merchandising" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Sheet Metal Trades" (color), undated (Box 34)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Suez Canal," (color), 1956 (Box 106)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "What's In It For Me?" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 81)
    - Louis de Rochemont films - "Work Supervisor" (color), undated (Box 37)
    - "Magic Mirror of Aloyse" (color), undated (Box 71)
    - Manufacturing Chemists Association (MCA) - "Fish Story"/"Fish Help Fight Pollution" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - Manufacturing Chemists Association (MCA) - "Fish Story"/"Fish Help Fight Pollution" (color original rolls), undated (Box 38)
    - Manufacturing Chemists Association (MCA) - "Smithsonian Plastics" (color), undated (Box 27)
    - Manufacturing Chemists Association (MCA) - "Smithsonian Plastics" (color original rolls), undated (Box 41)
    - Manufacturing Chemists Association (MCA) - "Smithsonian Plastics" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 66)
    - "Martin Luther" (b&w), undated (Box 112)
    - "Men to Match the Jungle" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 65)
    - "Millinery" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous (color), undated (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous outs, trims, and cuts (color), undated (Box 56)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Ancient Art for Modern Research" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 68)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Bag Your Trash" (color), undated (Box 29)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Bag Your Trash" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 68)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Bag Your Trash" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Catalysts"/"New Promise for Pollution Control" (color), undated (Box 25)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Clean Air Car" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Computer Trumps Credit Card Sharks" (color), undated (Box 57)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Computer Trumps Credit Card Sharks" (b&w inter-negative), undated (Box 15)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Computer Trumps Credit Card Sharks" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 66)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Futuristic Service Station" (color inter-negative), undated (Box 69)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation - "Garbage" (color original rolls), undated (Box 40)